candy-box.biz 2016-01-18

# Candybox

Privacy Policy and cookies

Canybox’s Privacy Policy and Cookies

1\. The inclusion of personal data in the files of LINK UP ADVERTISING, S.R.O.:

  * All such information the User provides through online web forms of the Website shall be collected and processed in files owned by LINK UP ADVERTISING, S.R.O. (hereinafter referred to as “LINK UP”) for the purposes of providing the services requested by the User, replying to their requests and keeping the User informed of the products and services marketed by LINK UP, including by way of electronic means. If you do not wish to receive this type of electronic correspondence (e-mails), you may so indicate by ticking the boxes provided for that purpose, or by sending an e-mail to administration@linkupadv.com. The completion of all information marked as mandatory on this Website is necessary in order to ensure optimum provision of the services offered to the User. If this data is not provided, LINK UP does not guarantee that the information and services requested may be offered, correctly supplied or meet the needs of the User. 

2\. Submission of data for staff selection:

  * Curriculum vitaes submitted by the User to LINK UP will be used for the sole purpose of responding to applications for employment related to jobs advertised. By providing your personal information, you acknowledge that the data provided is yours and is accurate and true. 

3\. Prohibition on registration by minors:

  * Persons under the age of 14 must obtain prior consent from their parents or guardians before providing their personal information to LINK UP. If you are a minor, please ask your parents or guardians to contact us first. 

4\. Third Party disclousure:

  * Canybox does not collect any personal identifiable data, and any statement otherwise must be considered as false. 

5\. Exercise of rights:

  * The User may exercise their rights to access, rectification, cancellation and opposition by sending an e-mail to administration@linkupadv.com or by writing to LINK UP ADVERTISING Sro, Podbabská 20, 160 00 Prague (Czech Republic). 

6\. Communication of information by the User:

  * Before providing personal information belonging to third parties, the User must obtain their prior express consent and inform the parties concerned of the terms of this Privacy Policy. The User undertakes to not hold LINK UP liable for any possible claim, fine or penalty it may be obliged to bear as a result of the User’s breach of the obligations set forth in this clause. 

7\. Cookies:

  * LINK UP may use cookies either directly or through third parties contracted for the provision of measurement services when the User accesses the Website. Cookies are files sent to the browser from a web server to record the User’s activities on the website. The cookies used by the Website do not themselves provide any personal information about the User. Through the use of cookies, the server hosting the Website may recognize the browser used by the User in order to make web browsing simpler, for example by granting access for users who have previously registered to areas, services, promotions or competitions reserved exclusively for users without having to register every time they visit the Website. Cookies are also used to measure website audience and traffic parameters and to monitor the progress and number of visits. The User can also change the settings on their browser in order to receive notification of the receipt of cookies and to prevent the installation of cookies on their hard drive. Please refer to your web browser’s instructions and manuals for further information. To use this Website, the User does not have to allow the installation of cookies sent by the Website or third parties acting on behalf of LINK UP; however, the User may have to log in each time for those services requiring previous registration or “login”.
